{
    "subject": "resource/The_Offence",
    "predicate": "property/country",
    "object": "resource/United_Kingdom",
    "human_readable": "The Offence was made in United Kingdom.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9190396666526794,
            "question": "What type of offence was committed in the United Kingdom?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44972360134124756,
            "question": "What country is associated with The Offence?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42640000581741333,
            "question": "Where did The Offence take place?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.29342299699783325,
            "question": "What year did The Offence occur?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2823660373687744,
            "question": "Who reported The Offence to the authorities?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2514985501766205,
            "question": "Were there any significant consequences resulting from The Offence?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22260704636573792,
            "question": "Is there any information available about the perpetrator of The Offence?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2126501351594925,
            "question": "Is there any information about the victim of The Offence?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1566036343574524,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about The Offence?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1471049040555954,
            "question": "Is there a record of The Offence in legal documents?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Offence was made in United Kingdom.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7258_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about The Offence?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7258_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any information about the victim of The Offence?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7258_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any information available about the perpetrator of The Offence?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7258_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7258_117.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7258_121.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7258_125.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7258_133.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7258_135.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7258_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7258_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7258_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7258_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7258_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information provided, I can see that there are several documents related to laws and regulations in the United Kingdom. \n\nThe triple you're asking me to evaluate is \"The Offence was made in United Kingdom.\" This implies that the offense or crime mentioned in the documents must have occurred within the United Kingdom.\n\nFrom the text:\n\n\"...the offences will only apply if the person is acting for, on behalf of, or with the intention to benefit a foreign power or intends that conduct will, or knows their conduct may, materially assist a foreign intelligence service.\"\n\nand\n\n\"(5) A person commits an offence under subsection (1) or (2) only if, at the time of the coercion or deception -\n\n(a) the person or the victim or both of them are in England or Wales,\"\n\nIt can be inferred that the offense must have occurred in England or Wales.\n\nTherefore, my answer would be:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe context information provided includes laws and regulations from the UK, specifically relating to offences involving foreign powers and intelligence services. The documents discuss offences under English law that apply to actions taken outside of England and Wales but which involve individuals or entities habitually resident in or national to the United Kingdom. These provisions indeed reflect offences made within the jurisdiction of the United Kingdom even if some elements occur extraterritorially, thus supporting the statement that \"The Offence was made in United Kingdom.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " Response: {'output': 'Yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}